Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the limited edition
Superman cake batter cookie dough
blizzard. Let me show you how to make
it. There are a few key ingredients you
need for this recipe. One is that cake
batter extract that you just saw. You
can get it pretty easily on Amazon, but
they probably have it at your local
grocery store as well. I also added a
couple drops of blue food coloring. That
is completely optional. It doesn't
affect the taste whatsoever. But this is
the real key ingredient. Birthday cake
flavored protein cookie dough. This
stuff is insanely good. It tastes
exactly like real raw cookie dough, but
it packs 15 g of protein per pouch. And
the texture is just so identical to real
cookie dough. It makes for the perfect
ninja creamy topping. And then we just
throw in a few rainbow sprinkles and
then you're good to